♪ We ♪
♪ Are the crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
红宝石们回来了?
The rubies are back?
她们开着那个小飞船来的
They showed up on their little ship
看起来很生气
acting very angry,
所以我让她们“中场休息”一下
so I put them in time-out.
我以为这件事已经解决了
I thought we were done with these guys.
你们回来干嘛
Why did you come back here?
放出来一个问问她们要干什么吧
Let's release one and just ask what they're up to.
哦!哦!能让我来选吗?
Ooh! Ooh!Can I pick?!
选吧
Go for it.
嗯
Hmm.
哦!就选腿腿吧!
Oh!Let's talk to Leggy!
腿腿?
Leggy?
我根据她们宝石的位置分别起了名字
I named them based on the placement of their gems.
她们是腿腿,膀子,脐脐,眼宝和,额,万事通
There's Leggy, Army, Navy,Eyeball, and, uh...Doc.
腿腿看上去最好说话
Leggy seems like the easiest to talk to.
腿腿,下来吧!
Leggy, come on down!
嘿!嗨,我叫史蒂文
Hey! Hi.I'm Steven.
你们回来地球做什么?
What brings you back to Earth?
呃...我也不知道?
Uh...I don't know?
哦,呃,我懂你
Oh, uh,I understand.
我以前也经常忘记为什么出任务
I used to forget why we'd go on missions all the time.
那我去那边站着好了
I'll just go stand over here then.
我们来试试膀子吧
Let's take a chance on Army.
下午好!
Good afternoon!
我要把你们撕成--
I'll tear you limb --
-哈?-嘿,别这样没礼貌
-Huh?-Hey.Don't be like that.
啥?!我要把--
Why, I ought to --
嗷
Aw.
-嘿,你干嘛...-下一个!
-Hey, what the...-Next!
呃...脐脐?
Uh...Navy?
要是我没记错的话,我们是来地球...
If I remember correctly,we were on Earth...
呃...
Uh...
太尴尬了
This is so embarrassing.
哦吼
Oh-ho.
哦 啊!
Oh. Aah!
啊!
Aah!
好吧 呃,眼宝?
Okay.Uh, eyeball?
我才不会跟你们讲任何东西!
I'm not telling y'all nothing about nothing!
剩下最后一个是...呃,万事通
The only one left now is, uh...Doc.
铁石英在哪?!
Where's Jasper?!
上次我们来,
Last time we came,
你骗我们玩那个蠢游戏!
you tricked us into playing that stupid game!
然后你又说,“她在海王星呢”
Then, you said,"She's on Neptune,"
所以我们又去找,她根本不在那!
so we looked,and she wasn't there!
她没在海王星
She wasn't on Neptune
也没在这蠢太阳系的任何一颗行星上!
or any other planet in this whole dang solar system!
快告诉我们她在哪
Tell us where she is right now.
别玩游戏,别耍伎俩,也别搞伪装
No games, no tricks,and no slick disguises.
对!
-Yeah!
嘿!
Hey!
我在这儿呢!
I'm right here!
她搞笑呢?这根本不可能骗--
Is she serious?There's no way this is gonna --
看!是铁石英!
Look! It's Jasper!
铁石英!我是红宝石编号1F4-Cut-4ND.
Jasper!I'm Ruby 1F4-Cut-4ND.
曾经参与过地球战役
I fought in the war for Earth.
呃...稍息
Uh...at ease.
我当时在第六区的战场,听到了你的传闻
I was on the ground in Facet 6 when I heard the tale
说是第九区宝宝基地有个石英很厉害
of the Facet 9 Kindergarten Quartz That Could.
他们说你戴着头盔从土地中蹦出来
They said you popped out of the ground with your helmet on
在日落之前干掉了80个水晶战士
and took out 80 crystal gems before the sun went down.
当我知道这次任务是为了找你
When I found out this mission was to look for you,
我差点没控记巨我记己!
I nearly dissipated my form!
很荣幸终于见到你
It is an honor to finally meet you.
对,那就是我!
Yup. That's me!
一直这么大个儿,从来没小过--
Always huge, never small,all the --
自打出生之日起!
all the time since I was made!
等下
Wait a minute.
你看起来和我想象中不一样啊
You look different than I thought you would.
哦,露馅了吧
Oh, here it is.
哦,我晒黑了一点,你造,太阳晒的嘛
Oh, you must mean my tan --you know, from the sun.
愚蠢的地球太阳!啊!
Stupid Earth sun!Ah!
我恨这颗星球!
I hate this planet!
诅咒这颗星球!
Curse this planet!
不管怎样,还好最后找到了你
Well, it's a good thing we finally found you.
黄钻在等着你回去
Yellow Diamond is awaiting your return.
我们现在马上带你回母星
We'll take you back to Homeworld right away.
不行!我是说--
No! I mean --
我,铁石英
I, Jasper,
已经决定呆在地球了
have decided to stay on Earth.
-啥?!-为啥!
-What?!-Why?!
对啊,为什么,铁石英?
Yeah, why, Jasper?
因为我要在这里看住这些家伙
Because I gotta stay here with these guys.
对,必须把她们关起来...为钻石们效力
Yep, gotta keep 'em prisoner... for the diamonds.
-铁石英-多么伟大的牺牲
-Jasper.-Such devotion.
好吧,黄钻肯定想知道这些事
Well, Yellow will definitely want to know about this.
你需要在最近的钻石基地做报告
You'll have to file a report at the nearest Diamond base.
钻石基地在哪?
Where's that?
路上是不是有经过?
passed it on our way here?
你们几个呆瓜!是在,呃...
You dummies!It's, uh...
是--嗯
It's -- Hmm.
在那儿呢!
It's there!
我要一路保持这个形态到月球?
I gotta hold this all the way to the moon?!
呃,我是说押持
Uh, hold this.
押持这些...犯人
Hold these...prisoners.
如果去月球的话得把这些叛军犯人带着
Gotta bring the rebel prisoners if we're going to the moon.
不能把她们放在这里没人看管
Can't leave them here unsupervised.
很好 上飞船!
Very well.To the ship!
你在搞什么?这根本成功不了
What are you doing?This isn't going to work.
你不能一直保持这个形态啊
You can't hold that form forever.
我能做到的
I can do this.
我们先去月球,再回来
We'll go to the moon,come back,
然后她们走就是了
and they'll leave us alone.
跟我一起演就行
Just play along.
哦,嘿!
Oh, hey!
你们几个也要当犯人吗?
You guys want to be prisoners, too?
不要
Not really.
好吧,就问问
All right.Just checking.
哇,这里面好大!
Whoa.It's huge in here!
我以为会超级挤的
I thought it'd be super-cramped.
嘿!这可不是去郊游!
Hey!This ain't no pleasure cruise!
说得对!
Yeah!
放尊重点,水-水货战士们!
Show some respect,you crystal germs!
对,教训下她们,铁石英!
Yeah,you tell 'em, Jasper!
地球上那么多水可不是水货嘛!
I bet they got those germs from Earth!
嗷,真倒霉!
Aw, curses!
不敢相信我们竟然被抓了!
I can't believe we've been caught!
还是被铁石英抓到的!
And by none other than Jasper!
真是气死我惹
I'm so cross over it.
对啊
Uh-huh.
都怪铁石英--就是她抓的我们
That sure is Jasper --the one that caught us.
气死惹
Harumph.
多么一种耻辱啊!
Of all the indignities!
千刀万剐随你,我自闭口不言
Do what you want.I'll never talk.
我倒希望你能闭嘴呢
Huh, I wish.
对啊,哈哈,她话真多
Yeah.She talks a lot!
快去那边坐着!
Go sit over there now!
哇哦,铁石英又强壮又风趣
Wow!Jasper's so funny and strong!
我也这么想呢!
I was just thinking that!
这太有趣了!
This is fun!
-铁石英!-啊,我是铁石英!
-Jasper!-Agh! I'm Jasper!
请你坐上我的位置,就在最前--
Please feel free to take my seat right up front --
那个船长座位
the captain's seat.
这是我的荣幸
It would be an honor.
好
Yeah.
好,没问题
Yes.Sure thing.
希望你觉得座位舒服
I hope it's to your liking.
还行吧
It's all right.
你可以随时
You can go ahead
驾驶飞船飞向月球基地
and head towards the moon base whenever you're ready.
但...
Buh...
当然可以!呵
Of course!Heh.
嗯
Hmm.
呃
Uh...
呃,听着
Uh, listen.
我是铁石英,我因为刚刚
I'm Jasper,and I'm too worn out
抓她们叛军上飞船所以很累
from catching rebels to fly,
所以我就坐这儿,像这样
so I'll just sit here,like this,
然后你驾驶飞船带我们上月球
and you work the thing to get us to the moon.
明白没?
Got it?
明白,当然的
Yes, of course.
那么,去月球?
To the moon, then?
对的,去月球!
To the moon, then!
我们即将到达月球
We'll be arriving shortly.
嘿,把座位捂热了
Hey, keep my seat warm
我去看看那些,呃,犯人们
while I check on our,uh, prisoners.
好的,铁石英,好主意
Yes, Jasper.Good idea.
不!
No!
离我们远点,你个莽夫!
Stay away from us,you brute!
低调点,珍珠
Tone it down, Pearl.
那个红宝石都想把你丢出太空去了
That one ruby wants to throw you out into space.
抱歉,太入戏了
Sorry.Got a bit carried away.
呃,你还好吗,紫晶?
Uh, you okay, Amethyst?
你已经保持这种形态超长时间了
You've been holding that form forever now.
我能控制住
I've got it under control.
嘿!我回去的时候那个座位最好还是热着的!
Hey, my seat better still be warm when I get over there!
警报解除!
All clear!
这边请,铁石英
Right this way,Jasper.
哦,铁石英,放过我们可好?
Oh, Jasper,won't you ever let us go?
看看这个地方--冻结在过去的状态
Look at this place --frozen in time.
第一纪元时代的基地
An era-one base.
她的第一纪元基地
Her era-one base.
真是悲剧,发生在她身上那些事
It was a tragedy,what happened to her.
那到底是谁啊?
Who is that anyway?
你昨天才出生的吗?!
Were you made
yesterday?!
那是粉钻
That is Pink Diamond.
铁石英,最好你来解释
Jasper, maybe it's best if you explain.
我来?不要
What, me? No.
不,你来
No, you do it.
我,这个,太触动我的情感了
I'm, like,too messed up about it.
我懂你
I understand.
她是你原本的钻石
She was your original diamond.
地球是粉钻的殖民地
Earth was Pink Diamond's colony.
一开始一切都进展顺利
Everything was going smoothly at first.
宝宝基地在孕育第一批士兵
Kindergartens were incubating their first soldiers,
大块,温润的石英--就像这个大个子一样--
big, warm pieces of quartz --like this mountain over here --
在这土地丰富的矿物质中被成功制造出来
were being created from its rich minerals with great success.
突然--砰!
Then -- bam!
粉钻下属的石英战士之一
One of Pink Diamond's very own quartz soldiers
发动了叛变然后一发不可收拾
started a rebellion and took it too far.
叛变发生时你在哪里?
Where were you when it happened?
哦,你造的,就在附近
Oh, you know, around.
我当时在场 我亲眼看到了
I was there.I saw it with my own eye.
我看到水晶战士的头领
I watched the leader of the crystal gems --
玫瑰石英--粉碎了粉钻!
Rose Quartz --shatter Pink Diamond!
不
No.
玫瑰石英才不会那么做!
Rose Quartz would never do that!
还-还有,确实,她是要打仗但是--
A-And, sure,she had to fight but --
她不会粉碎任何人的!
but she would never shatter someone!
嘿!遇到问题了
Hey!We got a problem.
控制台坏掉了 通讯器也不见了
The panel is broken.The communicator is gone!
这个中心没办法联系黄钻了
There's no way to contact Yellow Diamond from this hub.
-是水晶战士!-难以置信!
-Crystal gems!-Unbelievable!
-粗鲁!-没教养!
-Rude!-No respect!
看到了吧!
-See!
她们什么事都做得出来!
They'll stoop to anything!
我们得把你带回母星了
We'll have to take you to Homeworld
你得亲自做报告
to file a report in person.
我不能!
I can't!
我不能走!
I can't go!
-哈?-我没明白
Huh?-I don't understand.
-你什么意思?-发生啥事?
-What do you mean?-What's going on?
你猜怎么?
You know what?
你懂我的
You know me.
帮我个忙,回去母星
Do me a favor and go back home
然后替我做这个报告
and file the report for me.
我相信你的,士兵
I'm trusting you,soldier.
哇哦
Wow.
没问题!
Of course!
就这么决定了
That settles it.
好了,红宝石们,返回飞船!
All right, rubies,back to the ship!
真棒,紫晶!
-All right, Amethyst!
你真的坚持住了
You really held it together.
你做到了
You did it.
-我就说你行的-嗷-
-I told you you could.-Aw.
嘿,需要把你们捎回地球吗?
Hey, you need a ride back to Earth?
如果你想我还可以坐在你腿上,呃--
I could sit on your lap if you want, uh --
什么?!
What?!
我还是铁石英!
I'm still Jasper!
我们又被骗了?!
We've been tricked again?!
难以置信!
No way!
红宝石们,组合!
Rubies, assemble!
你们再也别想耍我们了!
We won't let you trick us again!
嘿,红宝石们!
Hey, rubies!
要打出去打!
If you're gonna fight,take it outside!
你不可能这么轻易摆脱我们的!
You can't get rid of us that easy!
我想她可以
I bet she can.
-史蒂文!
-Steven!
♪ I could even learn
how to love like you ♪
♪ Love like you ♪